(Stuart:)Was it ever a dress-up party?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Stuart:)Howard, didn't you tell me
it was a dress-up party?
Yeah. (chuckles)
(knocking on door)
(Stuart:)I was told this is where to go
if I'm mad at Howard.
(Penny:)May I take your cloak?
(Stuart:)Thanks.
(Stuart:)This thing kept getting caught
in the chain of my bike.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'll catch you up.
(Sheldon:)Uh, Penny is angry at Leonard,
Leonard's angry at me and Penny,
(Sheldon:)I'm angry at Leonard and Amy,
(Sheldon:)Raj is angry at Howard,
(Sheldon:)and I'm angry
at George R.R. Martin
(Sheldon:)'cause there are no new books
for me to spoil for Leonard.
(Stuart:)So what happened
with you and Howard?
(Raj:)Says I was talking too much
(Raj:)about dating Claire and Emily,
(Raj:)and I accused him
of being jealous.